{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Caleb Hutchinson",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2015 is Nick Fradiani.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Caleb Lee Hutchinson",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Caleb Lee Hutchinson",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2010 is Lee DeWyze.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Thunderstorm Artis",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2010 is Lee DeWyze.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Caleb Lee Hutchinson",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "David Cook.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Chayce Beckham",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Caleb Hutchinson",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2010 is Lee DeWyze.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2010 is Lee DeWyze.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2023 was Caleb Kennedy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2010 is Lee DeWyze.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Thunderstorm Artis.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Thunderstorm Artis",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Thunderstorm Artis",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen. He is a 23-year-old singer from Arkansas.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 is Chayce Beckham.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 was Chayce Beckham.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 was Chayce Beckham.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 is Chayce Beckham.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen. He is a 23-year-old singer from Arkansas.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 was Leah Thompson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 was Leah Thompson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 was Leah Thomas.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 is Chayce Beckham.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2022 is Chayce Beckham.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol 2010 is Lee DeWyze.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    }
  ]
}